wallpostsoftware.com 2019-08-29

# 

This privacy policy governs your use of the **WallPost Software Application** (the Application) for mobile devices that was created by   **Smart Management IT Solutions LLC**.  This Privacy Policy will explain what information we collect and how we collect it and how this information is used by us and the ways by which the information is protected. 

WallPost provides integrated business solutions that include: 

  1. Task Management
  2. HR Management
  3. Project Management
  4. CRM Solutions
  5. Finance Solutions
  6. Company Performance Evaluation

Accessibility to these modules will depend on the packages that you have subscribed.

**CONTENT**

  1. User Provided Information
  2. Data Sharing
  3. Communications
  4. Data Retention Policy & Managing Your Information
  5. Security
  6. Changes to this Privacy Policy
  7. Consent
  8. Compliance
  9. Contact Us

**A. User Provided Information**

This page informs you of our policies regarding the collection, use and disclosure of Personal Information we receive from users of the Site.

The Application obtains the information you provide when you download and register the Application. When you register with us and use the Application, you generally provide:

  1. your name, company name, email address, country, phone number, and other contact information for registration
  2. transaction-related information, such as when you make purchases, respond to any offers, or download or use applications from us; 
  3. information you provide us when you contact us for help;
  4. credit card information for purchase and use of the Application, and;

In addition, the Application may collect certain information automatically, including, but without limitation, the type of mobile device you use, your mobile devices unique device ID, the IP address of your mobile device, your mobile operating system, the type of mobile Internet browsers you use, and information about the way you use the Application.  

We use your Personal Information only for providing and improving the Site. By using the Site, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Information Collection and Use While using our Site, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you.

**B. Data Sharing**

We may disclose User-Provided and Automatically Collected Information:

  1. as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or meet regulations, legal process or enforceable governmental request;
  2. when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others;
  3. to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  4. with our trusted services providers who work on our behalf who do not have an independent use of the information we disclose to them, and have agreed to adhere to the rules set forth in this privacy statement.
  5. If Developer Company Name is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of this information, as well as any choices you may have regarding this information.

You can stop all collection of information by the Application easily by uninstalling the Application. You may use the standard uninstall processes as may be available as part of your mobile device or via the mobile application marketplace or network. You can also request to opt-out via email, at   info@smartmanagement-its.com

**C. Communications**

We may use your Personal Information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials. From time to time, we may use your personal information to send important notices, such as communications about purchases and changes to our terms, conditions, and policies. You can always “unsubscribe” to marketing email communications that you receive by clicking the unsubscribe button once you receive such mails or email us at info@smartmanagement-its.com 

**D. Data Retention Policy & Managing Your Information**

We will retain User-Provided data for as long as you use the Application and for a reasonable time thereafter. Please note that some or all of the User Provided Data may be required in order for the Application to function properly. We use the information we have to help verify accounts and activity, and to promote safety and security on and off of our Services, such as by investigating suspicious activity or violations of our terms or policies. We also use personal information to help us create, develop, operate, deliver, and improve our products. You can delete your account any time. When you delete your account, your data will be deleted off after a reasonable time.

We do not use the Application to knowingly solicit data from or market to children under the age of 13 or equivalent minimum age in the relevant jurisdiction without verifiable parental consent.. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with information without their consent, he or she should contact us at info@smartmanagement-its.com and we will delete such information from our files within a reasonable time.

**E. Security**

We are concerned about safeguarding the confidentiality of your information. We provide physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect information we process and maintain. We restrict access to personal information to our employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

If you use our Services for, we collect information about the purchase or transaction. This includes your payment information, such as your credit or debit card number and other card information, and other account and authentication information, as well as billing, shipping and contact details. To ensure total safety and security, we use advanced technology and security tools to ensure the highest form of security is guaranteed for all the sensitive data that we have collected.

**F. Changes to this Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 1st December 2015 and will remain in effect except with respect to any changes in its provisions in the future, which will be in effect immediately after being posted on this page. This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time for any reason. By accepting these terms and conditions of this agreement, you are agreeing to and bound by any changes or updates we make to this Policy. It is your sole responsibility to follow up and be updated with any changes to this Policy via our website. Your continued use of the Service after we post any modifications to the Privacy Policy on this page will constitute your acknowledgment of the modifications and your consent to abide and be bound by the modified Privacy Policy. You are advised to consult this Privacy Policy regularly for any changes, as continued use is deemed approval of all changes. You can check the history of this policy by [clicking here](https://wallpostsoftware.com/app/policyhistory)

**G. Consent**

By using the Application, you are consenting to our processing of your information as set forth in this Privacy Policy now and as amended by us. "Processing,” means using cookies on a computer/hand held device or using or touching information in any way, including, but not limited to, collecting, storing, deleting, using, combining and disclosing information, all of which activities will take place in the United States. If you reside outside the United States your information will be transferred, processed and stored there under United States privacy standards.

**H. Compliance**

The Privacy Policy is regularly reviewed to ensure that it complies with all the local laws and we have self-regulatory system to ensure there are checks and balances in the system. When we receive formal written complaints, we will contact the person who made the complaint to follow up. We work with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that we cannot resolve with our users directly.

Any misuse of this app to indulge in any illegal activity whether locally or internationally, the consumer will be wholly responsible for the actions and the company is indemnified from any legal action taken against above mentioned illegal activity.

**I. Contact us**

If you have any questions regarding privacy while using the Application, or have questions about our practices, please contact us via email at info@smartmanagement-its.com
